MySQL JDBC driver not available; using in-memory demo data instead.
Library ID rejected as expected: Password reset is only available using your registered email address
Password reset code sent to test-admin@example.com: 846970
Registered email accepted for password reset.
Password was reset and persisted successfully.
---PASSWORD_RESET_END---
MySQL JDBC driver not available; using in-memory demo data instead.
Admin can manage_users: true
Librarian can manage_books: true
Student can borrow_books: true
Student cannot manage_books: false
---PERMISSION_END---
MySQL JDBC driver not available; using in-memory demo data instead.
Borrow permission tests passed.
---BORROW_END---
